Adriana R. Mistodi

East London, Mobile: 07448172055
Email: adriana.mistodi@outlook.com

Personal Profile

I graduated in communication and public relations, which I gained the power of communications and public relations specialist.

I have successfully completed a funded Software Development Training course with Just IT Training. A twelve-week intensive bootcamp covering the fundamentals of Web and Software development. I am aiming to improve my skills further and grasp a better understanding of software languages (HTML (Hyper Text Markup Language), CSS3, JavaScript - Node.js, Python, SQLite, MySQL and MongoDB).

I would like to work as a Junior Developer to gain more skills and experience. I thrive working in a challenging environment to push my skills and limit.

Education and IT Training

November 2023 / Present Just IT Training Ltd, London

Digital Skills Bootcamp: Software Development

A twelve-week intensive bootcamp covering the fundamentals of

Web and Software development.

Languages: Visual Basic, Java and MySQL

2021-2022 CompTIA A+ studying, install, patching, troubleshooting and

Hardware replacement:

Self-taught watching videos of www.professormesser.com

2010-2013 University of "Vasile Alecsandri," Bacau – Romania

Bachelor's Degree Communication and Public Relations

Core Modules: Object - oriented to communicate effectively across a range of media

and digital platforms, strategic thinking, and a critical stance, ability to make an effective, ethical, and responsible contribution to the organization.

2004-2010 National College of Art "George Apostu," Bacau – Romania

High School in Choreography - Classical BALLET

IT Skills

Software Development Skills: Java, Python, SQLite and MySQL

Web Technology: HTML5, CSS3 & JavaScript

Core Programming Languages: JavaScript and Python

Projects:

Created a functional magic 8 ball – fortune teller, that spins and it gives a different answer every time you click on the ball. I've created it with HTML, CSS3 and JavaScript and I experienced more how to work with animations and shadows in a more efficient way. This project can be accessed

here: here: https://adrianaa911.github.io/FortuneTeller/

□ Created a functional grocery-list, where you can create your own list and clear it as w project, using HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript, I've learned how to work more with medi background color changes when you make the screen smaller) and how to give funct button. This project can be accessed here: https://adrianaa911.github.io/grocery	a query (the ionality to a
FinalVersion/	
☐ Created a Film application using Python and SQLite. This project allows you to view, a delete a record by using the CRUD method. This Film application can be accessed her https://replit.com/@adrianamistodi/filmflixApp	•
Employment History	

Linployment mistory

2018-2021 Beauty Sales Representative

- Identify and recommend products that fit the client's needs, preferences, and budget.
- Pitching relevant products or services, explaining how the products work and ensuring they have a positive experience from start to finish.
- Dealing with customer queries in a calm and professional manner.
- Make sales, process returns and maintain a balanced cash register.
- Demonstrating make-up techniques, suggesting products that meet client's needs and informing customers about product details like ingredients, application methods and price.

Nov.2017-Ian.2018 Temporary role	PMP Recruitment Ltd, Oriel House 55-57 Sheep Street Northampton NN1 2NE Warehouse Operative
☐ Use scanners to read b	ar codes on products.
0.	packing orders in a timely manner and working with targets, cleaning, and equipment to set standards.
☐ Meeting key performa	nce targets.
☐ Receive and put away i	nventory.
Nov.2014-Feb.2015	House of Fraser, PMP Recruitment
Temporary role	Milton Keynes, Warehouse Operative
☐ Sorting the items with	scanners to a target level.
☐ Processing orders, retu	ırns register damaged items.
☐ Ensure products meet	quality requirements.
☐ Cleaning and maintaini	ing warehouse equipment to set standards.
☐ Work effectively individ	dually and as a part of a team.

Dec.-2013-lan.2014 Homebased, Wellingborough Temporary role Picker: Warehouse Operative

- Processing-picking and packing orders in a timely manner and working with targets, cleaning, and maintaining warehouse equipment to set standards.
- Receive, put away, pick, pack, dispatch and process the brand returns.
- Meeting key performance targets, health and safety awareness.

Hobbies

☐ Solving puzzle game	es, memory games.
0.	keeping a healthy lifestyle.
☐ Learning different I Italian.	anguages. Currently improving my knowledge in languages such as Spanish and
\square Going on hikes. My	last hiking trip was up in the North, at the Peak District National Park.
Driving license:	Yes, Cat B.

Reference available upon request